Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Mr Dancho Hadzhiev
A Bulgarian Residing in Greece
My name is Dancho Hadziev.
I'm from Bulgaria but I reside in Thessaloniki, Greece.
Today, I have the grace to be here among you
to share with you my wonderful testimony
of what God has done for me.
I want to start from the beginning.
I was born in Bulgaria in a wealthy family.
For many years, whatever I wished, I could have.
As a result, when I went to junior high school,
I didn't care about anything
because my mother and father had great names in our howetown.
When I was in high school, I started a gang and we would harm people.
Anytime I did bad things,
when I had finished doing them, I realised that they were not good.
And yes, I kept doing them over and over again.
The evil things I did included beating other people,
taking their money
and making tattoos all over my body.
I had this thought that I was God.
A time came
when I didn't want to live the life I was living.
I had a dream since I was very young to become a police officer.
I entered the police force to become a police officer.
I must not forget that today is a day of truth.
When I went to school to become a police officer, things continued the same.
Although they taught us to be patient and humble and to do things the right away,
there was always something inside me that provoked me to do the opposite.
When I finished the school to become a police officer,
I became a police officer.
I thought I was the only one and there was nobody else apart from me.
Because of the authority I had, I made people feel bad.
In other words, I thought I was God.
These things did not cause me anything good.
Many of the people I had done bad things to, sued me as a police officer.
Higher ranking officers asked me what I was doing but I would not pay them any attention.
We have been listening to the experience of the brother, who said right from the young age he had joined a gang.
He was a bully at school and he oppressed people.
At some point he felt guilty about his bad attitude and he decided to fulfil his dream, that he had
right from the young age to become a police officer.
He went to the academy and he was trained as a police officer and later got employed in the police force
in his country, that is Greece.
He said that after he had joined the police force, because he was not yet delivered from that evil spirit
that had been tormenting his life, he still found himself doing the same thing
he had been doing right from his young age.
He said even as a police officer, rather than protect life and defend the oppressed, he found himself
being the one oppressing and bullying people, even as a police officer.
What experience can he share with the children of God; his attitude, oppression towards people,
as a police officer?
Mr Dancho Hadzhiev
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I will give you an example.
Whether I was in my uniform or not, I was the same.
I had the spirit of anger.
One day, when we had a mission,
as we were going to arrest someone,
I was inside the police car.
A simple citizen passed in front of the car that I was in.
Anger arose inside me and I rushed out of the police car.
I couldn't remember what happened next.
My colleagues told me that I rushed out of the car
and beat the man in a way that nobody had ever done before.
Afterwards, I realised that I did something very bad asking myself why I had done that.
I asked myself why I did this when I was supposed to be an example to others.
The day came when I was called in to see the Chief of Police.
He told me that he wanted to tell me something.
He said that it was either I stopped what I was doing or they would sack me.
It is bad for a police officer to be sacked; so, he should resign instead.
However, I didn’t do that.
Instead, I got angry and grabbed him by his neck.
I told him I didn't care what he would do, that I had money and everything I wanted
and that he should rather perish.
The time came when I was at home and I received a sack letter from the police force.
We have just heard from the brother who said that as a result of this spirit of anger in him, he got to a point
where he oppressed the citizen of his country while being on a mission to arrest somebody.
On their way, an ordinary citizen passed in front of their vehicle.
He rushed of a car in anger, grabbed that man, and beat him mercilessly.
He said that he didn't remember what he had done to this man, which proves that an evil spirit was behind
that anger.
It was his colleagues that told him of that great offence he committed beating this man mercilessly.
As a result, he was called to his superior in the police force.
They advised him saying that what he was doing was bad for the image of the police force.
They gave him a choice to stop or be sacked.
Instead of feeling remorse or guilt for what he had done, he became angry; he grabbed the superior officer,
he shook him and told him that he had money and he could do anything.
Few days later he received a sack letter from the police force.
When they gave me the sack letter, I was very unhappy.
So, since I already had a bad reputation, I made the decision to continue the same lifestyle.
I got involved with the mafia.
Because I knew many people in the police force, I could do whatever I wanted.
I started having friends who were smoking cannabis and drinking.
So, I was doing the same thing as a young man in the world.
I got very frustrated with what I was doing but couldn't stop it.
Every time I did something evil, I would tell myself that it was the last time.
I couldn't stop; I would do it again and again
Many times, I tried on my own to stop smoking,
drinking alcohol and the lifestyle I was living
because I knew that that lifestyle was not normal.
Something inside of me was telling me that there was a plan for me.
We heard from the brother who said that he always had felt he could not get out of his problem on his own.
Can you tell us what happened that led to your deliverance?
Mr Dancho Hadzhiev
Emmanuel TV Testimony
One day, when I was at home, a man from Bulgaria that I didn’t know, came to visit me.
He started talking to me about Jesus Christ but I told him that I already knew Him.
I told him to tell me something new and he asked me to sit down and said he would.
As we were talking, he introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
This man was very patient with me because I was behaving badly.
Through his mobile phone, he opened Emmanuel TV.
He started showing me videos of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The first time I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua, I wondered, “Is this African man healing people?
He must be a fraudster”.
However something within me was telling me that I should not talk like that
because if truly God had covered him with His blood, I would be in trouble.
So, I stopped talking in that way to the man who was sitting beside me.
Since that day, I started watching Emmanuel TV all day long.
Sunday came and it was a live service at The SCOAN.
Within me, I decided to dedicate the day to watch Emmanuel TV and see what was happening.
As I was watching, I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua praying for people.
I was thinking to myself, ‘Lord, if You are truly there in this Church,
as this man is praying, if You are the Healer, Deliverer, Redeemer, and everything,
help me to believe this and see that it’s true’.
Then, I received the answer.
Since that time, my life changed!
Mr Dancho Hadzhiev
Emmanuel TV Testimony
My life changed and I stopped smoking.
I will start from the smaller things that the Lord has done for me.
Before, I was a very big gambler.
I stopped gambling.
I stopped smoking cannabis, drinking alcohol and doing anything that had to do with the world.
However, I will tell you the greatest thing that the Lord has done for me.
Because of all the things I was doing, I had many court cases.
The Lord made all these cases disappear!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Put your hands together for the miracle working God, for what He has done in the life of this brother!
Hallelujah!
In this way I received the greatest miracle.
They called me from the police force, asking me to come back and speak with them.
I went there and was re-hired for the same job!
Mr Dancho Hadzhiev
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I am now a special agent and the head of my team in the police force.
Hallelujah!
Put your hands together louder for the miracle working God!
I know that this testimony have lifted your faith to another level.
Brother standing right before us was deep into the world.
This thing cost him a lot.
It cost him his job, his reputation in the society, he was affected both emotionally and physically.
But in the moment Jesus Christ got into his life; He healed and delivered him completely and effectually.
Put your hands together louder for the miracle working God!
Hallelujah!
Our brother said something; a comment he made - "What can an African brother do to you?"
Now, that God Almighty has used His Prophet to deliver you and set you free -
what can you say about the ministry of Prophet T.B. Joshua?
I want to tell people all over the world who are hearing this testimony today
who have spoken negative words about this ministry and Prophet T.B. Joshua
to go and ask for forgiveness from the Lord.
Because Prophet T.B. Joshua is a true prophet and a real man of God.
What is your advice to millions of people that are listening to you right now?
What advise do you have for them all?
My advice to those in the same situation I once was in or facing another problem -
don’t run away from God but run to Him.
They have to go through this situation with God.